Greene Cattle Company collection 1836-1970
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Maps
  This is a small collection of county and ranch maps concerning the holdings of the Greene Cattle Company.
  - Diamond Seven Ranch, Seligman, Arizona, 1951-1954 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - General, 1952-1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Luis Maria Baca Float, Seligman, Arizona, 1933-1958 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Palominas Ranch, Hereford, Arizona (1 of 2), 1933-1952 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Palominas Ranch, Hereford, Arizona (2 of 2), 1957-1961 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - San Rafael Ranch, Santa Cruz County, Arizona, 1947-1958 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Series V: Oversized
  This includes 29 oversized boxes the majority of which are the financial ledgers of the Greene Cattle Company. A few boxes contain other items of interest including photographs, memorabilia, and a rare book from 1910 titled Recuerdo del Centenario de la Independencia Mexicana Las Fiestas en Cananea, Sonora. This series is organized by subject and then chronologically within.
  - Financial Ledgers – Expense Statements, 1919-1928 (Box 23)
  - Financial Ledgers - General Ledger, 1927-1928 (Box 24, Folder A)
  - Financial Ledgers - Lost Cost Records, 1938-1940 (Box 24, Folder B)
  - Financial Ledgers - Green Cattle Company of Arizona, 1927-1929 (Box 25, Folder A)
  - Financial Ledgers - Greene Cattle Company of California, 1928-1930 (Box 25, Folder B)
  - Financial Ledgers - Expense Ledger, 1929-1931 (Box 26)
  - Financial Ledgers - Expense Statements, 1929-1931 (Box 27)
  - Financial Ledgers - Untitled, 1929-1932 (Box 28)
  - Financial Ledgers - Greene Cattle Company of California, 1930-1932 (Box 29, Folder A)
  - Financial Ledgers - Greene Cattle Company and San Pasqual Land and Cattle Company Records, 1933-1938 (Box 29, Folder B)
  - Financial Ledgers - Greene Cattle Company and San Pasqual Land and Cattle Company Records, 1935-1937 (Box 29, Folder C)
  - Financial Ledgers - Salt River Valley Cattle Sales, 1938-1941 (Box 29, Folder D)
  - Financial Ledgers - Salt River Valley Cattle Lost Cost Record, 1941 (Box 29, Folder E)
  - Financial Ledgers - General Ledger Arizona Division, 1930-1935 (Box 30)
  - Financial Ledgers - General Ledger, Journal, Cash Records, Checks Drawn, Voucher Records, 1931-1934 (Box 31)
  - Financial Ledgers - Miscellaneous Notes Record, Lots Sold Out, 1934-1942 (Box 32)
  - Financial Ledgers - General Ledger, Journal, Cash Records, Checks Drawn, Voucher Records, 1935-1937 (Box 33)
  - Financial Ledgers - Accounts Ledger, 1936-1937 (Box 34)
  - Financial Ledgers - Analysis Sheets Various Accounts, 1937-1938 (Box 35, Folder A)
  - Financial Ledgers - General Ledger California Division, 1937-1941 (Box 35, Folder B)
  - Financial Ledgers - General Ledger Arizona Division, 1937-1941 (Box 36)
  - Financial Ledgers - California and Arizona Division Journal of Cattle Accounts, 1937-1942 (Box 37)
  - Financial Ledgers - Division Reports, Checks Issued, Cattle Reports, Feed Reports, 1938-1942 (Box 38, Folder A)
  - Financial Ledgers - California and Arizona Divisions Combined, 1942-1949 (Box 38, Folder B)
  - Financial Ledgers - Lost Cost Records and Analysis Sheets, Arizona and California Division, 1941-1943 (Box 39)
  - Financial Ledgers - Lost Cost Records, Inventories, Depreciation Schedule, Analysis Sheets, 1941-1947 (Box 40)
  - Financial Ledgers - Journal Records and Ledger, 1942 (Box 41)
  - Financial Ledgers - Cash Received, Checks Drawn, Daily Bank Balance, 1942-1944 (Box 42)
  - Financial Ledgers - Payroll Records, 1942-1945 (Box 43)
  - Financial Ledgers - Journal of Original Entries, Division Reports, Etc., 1943-1945 (Box 44)
  - Financial Ledgers - Cash Received, Checks Drawn, Daily Bank Balances, 1944-1946 (Box 45)
  - Financial Ledgers - Records of Original Entries, Expense Ledger, 1945-1946 (Box 46, Folder A)
  - Financial Ledgers - Payroll Records, 1945-1948 (Box 46, Folder B)
  - Financial Ledgers - Expense Details and Inventories, 1947-1948 (Box 47, Folder A)
  - Financial Ledgers - Division Reports and Other Records, 1948 (Box 47, Folder B)
  - General- Correspondence pp.1-469 (from bound volume), 1906-1910 (Box 48, Folder A)
  - General- Recuerdo del Centenario de la Independencia Mexicana Las Fiestas en Cananea, Sonora, 1910 (Box 48, Folder B)
  - Legal and Maps - Greene Cattle Company Meeting Minutes, 1905-1908 (Box 49, Folder A)
  - Legal and Maps - Township 23 Sections and Platts (Box 49, Folder B)
  - Memorabilia – 2 Pistols, Leather Holster, 2 Spurs, Company Seal Stamp, Greene Cartoon Engraving, ND (Box 50)
  - Photographs - Col. Greene at Cananea facing an angry mob, 1905 (Box 51, Folder A)
  - Photographs - Johnny Mullins and his favorite horse Wino at Oro Ranch Stage Station (Includes a letter from Margarethe Greene describing the photograph), 1968 (Box 51, Folder B)
  - Photographs - Interview with Johnny Mullins, Greene Cattle Company Ranch, audio cassette, 1970 (Box 51, Folder C)
  - Photographs - Charles E. Wiswall, Undated (Box 51, Folder D)